quotelicious.com 2010-01-02

# QuoteLicious - Privacy Policy

| 

 Quotes

 Celebrity

 TV Movie

 Links

 Misc

| 

Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). 

We do not collect any information about our visitor's email or referring domain. 

For visitors on our website we collect Aggregate (General Tracking) information about pages that users visit on our site. 

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site. 

With respect to cookies: We do not set any cookies. 

However, third parties may be placing and reading cookies on browsers, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on quotelicious.com. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. 

However, some some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

If you have any questions feel free to email me at: quotelicious.com@gmail.com 

|  |
